Finding aid for the Albert Kahn Associates records, 1825-2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Construction Photographs, 1902-1982
  - Job No. 1752-1992
    - Dodge Truck Division, Chrysler Corporation, Addition to Assembly Building No. 101, Macomb County, MI, (1945-1946), Job No. 1766-P (Box 50)
    - Dodge Truck Division, Chrysler Corporation, Addition to Boiler House No. 103, Macomb County, MI, (1945-1946), Job No. 1766-Q (Box 50)
    - Ford Motor Company, Press Building, Dearborn, MI, (1937-1938), Job No. 1772, 4 folders (Box 50)
    - United Air Lines, Office Building, Chicago, IL, (1937-1938), Job No. 1776 (Box 50)
    - United Air Lines, General Office Building Addition, Chicago, IL, (1941-1942), Job No. 1776-B (Box 50)
    - Ford Motor Company Exposition Building, New York World's Fair, (1938-1940) Job No. 1783, 1939
      - Early Construction of Building by Knickerbocker Photo Service, 3/15/1938-4/26/1938; 12 prints (black-and-white; 7-1/2x9-1/2-inch) (Box 9)
      - Construction of Building by Albert Rothschild, Commercial Photographer, 104 prints (black-and-white; 7-1/2x9-1/2-inch)
        - 1, 5/4/1938-10/27/1938; 51 prints (Box 9)
        - 2, 11/3/1938-4/28/1939; 53 prints (Box 9)
      - Construction of Building Alterations by unknown photographer, 96 prints (black-and-white; 7-1/2x9-1/2-inch)
        - 1, 1/18/1940-2/29/1940; 45 prints (Box 9)
        - 2, 3/7/1940-5/1/1940; 51 prints (Box 9)
      - Albert Kahn and Others, Surveying Construction, 8/20/1940; 1 prints (black-and-white; 5x7-1/2-inch) (Box 9)
    - General Motors Corporation Exposition Building, New York World's Fair, (1938-1939) Job No. 1784-A
      - Construction of Building by Eric J. Baker, Elizabeth, N. J., 77 prints (black-and-white; 7-1/2x9-1/2-inch) (Box 10)
        (64 prints by Baker and 13 prints by unknown photographer)
        - 1, 8/1/1938-10/20/1938; 36 prints (Box 10)
        - 2, 10/25/1938-3/21/1939; 41 prints (Box 10)
      - Construction of Foundation by unknown photographer, 8/10/1938-8/30/1938; 25 prints (black-and-white; 2-3/4x4-1/2 inch), 4 prints (black-and-white; 3x5-inch) (Box 10)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Curtiss Airplane Division, Buffalo, New York (1938) Job No. 1785
      - Construction of Dope Room and Zinc Foundry by unknown photographer, 3/19/1938-4/9/1938, 14 prints (black-and-white; 2-3/4x4-1/2-inch) (Box 4)
    - Kalamazoo School District, Additions and Alterations to Existing School Building, Kalamazoo, MI, (1938-1939), Job No. 1792 (Box 50)
    - General Motors Corporation, Buick Motor Division, Overhead Traffic Bridge, Flint, MI, (1938-1939), Job No. 1795 (Box 50)
    - General Motors Corporation, Buick Motor Division, Service Parts Storage Building, Flint, MI, (1938-1940), Job No. 1795 (Box 50)
    - General Motors Corporation, Buick Motor Division, Rear Axle Building, Flint, MI, (1940), Job No. 1795-A (Box 51)
    - General Motors Corporation, Buick Motor Division, Administration Building Addition, Flint, MI, (1956), Job No. 1795-AP (Box 51)
    - General Motors Corporation, Buick Motor Division, Building No. 71-B, Flint, MI, (1950-1951), Job No. 1795-Q (Box 51)
    - General Motors Corporation, Buick Motor Division, Building No. 36, Flint, MI, (1950-1952), Job No. 1795-S (Box 51)
    - General Motors Corporation, Buick Motor Division, Building No. 43, Flint, MI, (1951-1952), Job No. 1795-T (Box 51)
    - Toledo Scale Company, Office and Factory Building, Toledo, OH, (1939), Job No. 1799 (Box 51)
    - Toledo Scale Company, Factory Building and Boiler House Extension, Toledo, OH, (1941), Job No. 1799-A (Box 51)
    - Toledo Scale Company, North Side Factory Building Addition, Toledo, OH, (1942), Job No. 1799-C (Box 51)
    - Toledo Scale Company, Factory Building and Boiler House Additions, Toledo, OH, (1947-1948), Job No. 1799-D, E (Box 51)
    - Toledo Scale Company, Factory Building North Addition, Toledo, OH, (1948), Job No. 1799-F (Box 51)
    - Niles-Bement-Pond Company, Pratt and Whitney Division, Factory and Office Buildings, Garage, Pattern Shop, Boiler House, West Hartford, CT, (1939-1940), Job No. 1800 A, B (Box 51)
    - Niles-Bement-Pond Company, Pratt and Whitney Division, Die Storage Building, West Hartford, CT, (1940-1941), Job No. 1800-D (Box 51)
    - Niles-Bement-Pond Company, Pratt and Whitney Division, Factory Building, Northwest Corner Extension, West Hartford, CT, (1941), Job No. 1800-E (Box 51)
    - Niles-Bement-Pond Company, Pratt and Whitney Division, Machine Tool Building, West Hartford, CT, (1942), Job No. 1800-H (Box 51)
    - Niles-Bement-Pond Company, Pratt and Whitney Division, Gauge Building, West Hartford, CT, (1942), Job No. 1800-J (Box 51)
    - R.C.A. Manufacturing Company, Inc., Addition to Indianapolis Plant, Camden, NJ, (1939), Job No. 1802 (Box 51)
    - Keyston Steel and Wire Company, Office Building, Peoria, IL, (1939), Job No. 1803 (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Vought-Sikorsky Division, Proposed Addition to Factory Building, Stratford, CT, (1939), Job No. 1804 (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Vought-Sikorsky Division, 400 Foot Addition to Manufacturing Plant, Stratford, CT, (1940-1941), Job No. 1804-A (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Vought-Sikorsky Division, Factory Building Extension and New Office Addition, Stratford, CT, (1942-1943), Job No. 1804-B (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Division, Office Building Extension, Stratford, CT, (1943-1944), Job No. 1804-F (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Division, Two Story Factory Addition, Stratford, CT, (1943-1944), Job No. 1804-G, 2 folders (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Division, Main Boiler Plant Addition, Stratford, CT, (1943-1944), Job No. 1804-H (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Division, South Factory Plant Spray Booth, Stratford, CT, (1943), Job No. 1804-J (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Division, Revision and Addition to Electric Distribution System, Stratford, CT, (1943), Job No. 1804-K (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Division, Scrap Segregation Building, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1804-L (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Division, Paint Storage Building, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1804-M (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Division, West Employees Entrance, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1804-N (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Division, Fire House, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1804-O (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Division, Cafeteria Alterations, Stratford, CT, (1944-1945), Job No. 1804-R (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Division, Incinerator Building, Stratford, CT, (1945), Job No. 1804-V (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Division, Paint Storage Building Alterations and Addition, Stratford, CT, (1945), Job No. 1804-W (Box 51)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Division, Alterations to Building for Sheridan Stretch Press Area 51 Main Plant, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1804-X (Box 51)
    - Ohio Steel Foundry Company, Roll and Heavy Machine Shop, Lima, OH, (1939), Job No. 1806 (Box 51)
    - Ohio Steel Foundry Company, Breech Ring Plant, Lima, OH, (1942-1943), Job No. 1806-B (Box 51)
    - Ohio Steel Foundry Company, Machine Shop Addition, Lima, OH, (1942), Job No. 1806-C (Box 52)
    - Ohio Steel Foundry Company, Personnel Building, Lima, OH, (1943), Job No. 1806-D (Box 52)
    - Ohio Steel Foundry Company, Roll and Heavy Machine Shop Addition, Lima, OH, (1951-1952), Job No. 1806-J (Box 52)
    - Ohio Steel Foundry Company, Forge Shop, Lima, OH, (1957-1958), Job No. 1806-K, 3 folders (Box 52)
    - Hanes Hosiery Mills Company, Knitting Mills, Winston-Salem, NC, (1939), Job No. 1807 (Box 52)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Oakland Parts Warehouse, San Leandro, CA, (1939), Job No. 1808 (Box 52)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Body Building, San Leandro, CA, (1951-1953), Job No. 1808-C, 3 folders (Box 52)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Alterations at Southwest Corner of Body Building for Propeller Press and Furnace, San Leandro, CA, (1952-1953), Job No. 1808-E (Box 52)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Enclosure for Paint Rooms, Fire Walls, and Conveyor Bridge from Body to Assembly Building, San Leandro, CA, (1952-1953), Job No. 1808-F (Box 52)
    - Heald Machine Company, New Office Building and Factory Building, Worcester, MA, (1939-1940), Job No. 1811-A (Box 52)
    - Heald Machine Company, Office Building, Worcester, MA, (1940), Job No. 1811-B (Box 52)
    - United Airlines Transport Corporation, Office Building and Hangar, Portland, OR, (1940), Job No. 1827 (Box 52)
    - Aviation Manufacturing Corporation, Stinson Aircraft Division, Factory and Office Building, Nashville, TN, (1939-1940), Job No. 1828 (Box 52)
    - B.F. Goodrich Company, Addition to Southeast Corner of Present Plant, Oaks, PA, (1943), Job No. 1840-E (Box 52)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Curtiss Aeroplane Division, Factory and Office Building, Boiler House, Truck Garage, Oil Storage, Switch House, Buffalo, NY, (1940-1941), Job No. 1841 A, B, C, D, 1 folder (Box 52)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Curtiss Aeroplane Division, Factory and Office Building, Boiler House, Truck Garage, Oil Storage, Switch House, Buffalo, NY, (1940-1941), Job No. 1841 A, B, C, D, 1 folder (Box 53)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Curtiss Aeroplane Division, Final Assembly Bay Extension, East and West Additions to Airport Plant No. 2, Boiler House Addition, Manufacturing Building Addition, Drop Hammer Building, Office Building Extension, Expansion Program, Buffalo, NY, (1942-1944), Job No. 1841-K, L, M, O, P, R, W, X (Box 53)
    - Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corporation, Ranger Engineering Corporation Division, Factory Additions, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1940), Job No. 1843-A, B, C (Box 53)
    - Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corporation, Ranger Aircraft Engines Division, Engine Test Houses, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1941), Job No. 1843-E (Box 53)
    - Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corporation, Ranger Aircraft Engines Division, Factory and Office Building Additions, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1941), Job No. 1843-F (Box 53)
    - Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corporation, Ranger Aircraft Engines Division, Hangar, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1942), Job No. 1843-G (Box 53)
    - Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corporation, Ranger Aircraft Engines Division, Addition to South Side of Present Building, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1942), Job No. 1843-K, 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corporation, Ranger Aircraft Engines Division, Boiler House Alterations and Additions, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1942-1943), Job No. 1843-L (Box 53)
    - The Sherwin-Williams Company, Chemical Products Building, Chicago, IL, (1940-1941), Job No. 1845 (Box 53)
    - The Sherwin-Williams Company, Warehouse Building, Chicago, IL, (1940-1941), Job No. 1845-A (Box 53)
    - The City Machine and Tool Company, Factory Building, Toledo, OH, (1940), Job No. 1846 (Box 53)
    - Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Company, Enameling Building, Mansfield, OH, (1940), Job No. 1847 (Box 53)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Propeller Division, New Boiler House, Caldwell, NJ, (1940-1941), Job No. 1853 (Box 53)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Propeller Division, Factory and Office Building, Caldwell, NJ, (1940-1941), Job No. 1853-A (Box 53)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Propeller Division, Administration Building, Caldwell, NJ, (1940-1941), Job No. 1853-B (Box 53)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Propeller Division, Factory Extension, Caldwell, NJ, (1940-1941), Job No. 1853-F (Box 53)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Propeller Division, Sewage Disposal Plant, Caldwell, NJ, (1940), Job No. 1853-G (Box 53)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Propeller Division, Propeller Test Cells, Caldwell, NJ, (1943), Job No. 1853-L (Box 53)
    - Ethyl Gasoline Corporation, New Engineering Research Building, Ferndale, MI, (1940-1942), Job No. 1854 (Box 53)
    - Ethyl Gasoline Corporation, Alterations and Additions to Plant, Ferndale, MI, (1954-1955), Job No. 1854-M (Box 53)
    - Jacobs Manufacturing Company, Factory and Office Building, Boiler House, Hartford, CT, (1940-1941), Job No. 1857 A (Box 53)
    - Jacobs Manufacturing Company, Factory and Office Building Addition, Hartford, CT, (1947-1948), Job No. 1857-B (Box 53)
    - Jacobs Manufacturing Company, Addition to East Side of Plant, Hartford, CT, (1951-1952), Job No. 1857-D (Box 53)
    - Taylorcraft Aviation Corporation, Aircraft Plant, Alliance, OH, (1940), Job No. 1859 (Box 53)
    - Todd Shipyards Corporation, Robins Dry Dock and Repair Company, Personnel Building, Brooklyn, NY, (1940-1941), Job No. 1860-A (Box 54)
    - Todd Shipyards Corporation, Robins Dry Dock and Repair Company, Compressed Air Systems, Brooklyn, NY, (1940-1941), Job No. 1860-B (Box 54)
    - Todd Shipyards Corporation, Robins Dry Dock and Repair Company, Manufacturing and Storage Building, Brooklyn, NY, (1941-1942), Job No. 1860-C (Box 54)
    - Todd Shipyards Corporation, Robins Dry Dock and Repair Company, Blacksmith Shop, Brooklyn, NY, (1941-1942), Job No. 1860-F (Box 54)
    - Todd Shipyards Corporation, Robins Dry Dock and Repair Company, Boiler House, Brooklyn, NY, (1941-1942), Job No. 1860-G (Box 54)
    - Todd Shipyards Corporation, Robins Dry Dock and Repair Company, Substation, Brooklyn, NY, (1941-1942), Job No. 1860-K (Box 54)
    - Todd Shipyards Corporation, Robins Dry Dock and Repair Company, Garage and Locker Rooms, Brooklyn, NY, (1941-1942), Job No. 1860-L (Box 54)
    - Fairchild Aircraft Corporation, Manufacturing Plant, Hagerstown, MD, (1940-1941), Job No. 1861 (Box 54)
    - Fairchild Aircraft Corporation, Factory Additions, Hagerstown, MD, (1941-1942), Job No. 1861-B (Box 54)
    - Fairchild Aircraft Corporation, New Hangar Building, Hagerstown, MD, (1943-1944), Job No. 1861-J (Box 54)
    - Fairchild Aircraft Corporation, Manufacturing Building East Addition, Hagerstown, MD, (1943-1944), Job No. 1861-K, 5 folders (Box 54)
    - Fairchild Aircraft Corporation, Sewage Treatment Plant, Hagerstown, MD, (1943-1944), Job No. 1861-M (Box 54)
    - Fairchild Aircraft Corporation, Main Sewers, Hagerstown, MD, (1944), Job No. 1861-N (Box 54)
    - Fairchild Aircraft Corporation, Flight Test Hangar, Hagerstown, MD, (1945), Job No. 1861-X (Box 54)
    - City of Denver, Municipal Hangar Building No. 3, Denver, CO, (1940-1941), Job No. 1862 (Box 54)
    - General Electric Company, Materials and Processes Laboratory Building, Schenectady, NY, (1960), Job No. 1865-D (Box 54)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Vought-Sikorsky Aircraft Division, Engineering Building Addition, Stratford, CT, (1940-1941), Job No. 1866 (Box 54)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Vought-Sikorsky Aircraft Division, Experimental Building Addition, Stratford, CT, (1942), Job No. 1866-A (Box 54)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Vought-Sikorsky Aircraft Division, Test Hangar Building, Stratford, CT, (1942-1944), Job No. 1866-B (Box 54)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Plant Intercepting Sanitary Sewer, Stratford, CT, (1943), Job No. 1866-F (Box 54)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Vought-Sikorsky Aircraft Division, Test Hangar Building No. 2, Stratford, CT, (1943-1944), Job No. 1866-G (Box 54)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, S-44 Building Alterations, Stratford, CT, (1943-1944), Job No. 1866-H (Box 54)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Experimental Hangar, Stratford, CT, (1943-1944), Job No. 1866-J (Box 54)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, South Employees Entrance, Stratford, CT, (1943), Job No. 1866-K (Box 54)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Airplane Test Building, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1866-L (Box 54)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Three Story Addition to Engineering Building, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1866-M (Box 54)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, S-44 Building Alterations, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1866-P (Box 54)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Universal Test Jig Foundation, Stratford, CT, (1944-1945), Job No. 1866-Q (Box 54)
    - Chrysler Corporation Tank Arsenal, Warren, Michigan (1940-1943) Job No. 1867
      - Construction of Plant by unknown photographers, 7-1/2x10-inch, black-and-white prints (Box 5)
        - 1, 8/29/1940-9/27/1940; 33 prints (Box 5)
        - 2, 10/4/1940-10/25/1940; 35 prints (Box 5)
        - 3, 11/1/1940-11/22/1940; 38 prints (Box 5)
        - 4, 11/29/1940-12/20/1940; 38 prints (Box 5)
        - 5, 12/27/1940-1/17/1941; 44 prints (Box 5)
        - 6, 1/20/1941-2/14/1941; 34 prints (Box 5)
        - 7, 2/21/1941-3/21/1941; 32 prints (Box 5)
        - 8, 3/24/1941-5/29/1941; 35 prints (Box 5)
        - 9, 6/17/1941-1/4/1943; 7 prints (7x9-inch), 39 prints (8x10-inch) (Box 5)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Tank Arsenal, Macomb County, MI, (1941), Job No. 1867 (Box 55)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Factory and Office Building, Robertson, MO, (1940-1941), Job No. 1868, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Factory and Office Building, Columbus, OH, (1941), Job No. 1869 (Box 55)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, New Assembly Building, Columbus, OH, (1942-1943), Job No. 1869-J (Box 55)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Flight Office Addition, Columbus, OH, (1944), Job No. 1869-M (Box 55)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Firewall around Flight Hangar, Columbus, OH, (1944), Job No. 1869-P (Box 55)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Storage Tank in Flight Hangar, Columbus, OH, (1944), Job No. 1869-R (Box 55)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Service Building, Columbus, OH, (1943), Job No. 1869-T (Box 55)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Water Conservation Program, Columbus, OH, (1944), Job No. 1869-V (Box 55)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Fire and Police Station Building, Columbus, OH, (1944), Job No. 1869-W (Box 55)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Maintenance Building Addition, Columbus, OH, (1944), Job No. 1869-Y (Box 55)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Storage Building Addition, Columbus, OH, (1944), Job No. 1869-Z (Box 55)
    - Wright Aeronautical Corporation, New Magnesium Foundry Building, Fairlawn, NJ, (1940-1941), Job No. 1870 (Box 55)
    - Wallace Laboratories, Office and Manufacturing Building, North Brunswick, NJ, (1941-1942), Job No. 1871 (Box 55)
    - Wright Aeronautical Corporation, Machine, Assembly, and Office Buildings, Cincinnati, OH, (1940-1941), Job No. 1874, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Wright Aeronautical Corporation, North and South Shops, Magnesium and Aluminum Foundries, Test Cells, Boiler House, Compressor Buildings, Water Storage, Salvage and Refuse Building, Lockland, OH, (1942), Job No. 1874-AA -- AZ, 4 folders (Box 55)
    - Wright Aeronautical Corporation, North and South Shops, Magnesium and Aluminum Foundries, Test Cells, Boiler House, Compressor Buildings, Water Storage, Salvage and Refuse Building, Lockland, OH, (1942), Job No. 1874-AA -- AZ, 1 folder (Box 56)
    - Wright Aeronautical Corporation, Test Cells and Storage Building, Lockland, OH, (1941), Job No. 1874-C (Box 56)
    - Wright Aeronautical Corporation, Foundry Building, Lockland, OH, (1940-1941), Job No. 1874-D (Box 56)
    - Republic Aviation Corporation, Manufacturing and Assembly Building, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1941), Job No. 1878, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Republic Aviation Corporation, Boiler House, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1941), Job No. 1878-A (Box 56)
    - Republic Aviation Corporation, Experimental and Engineering Building No. 55 Alterations and Additions, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1955-1956), Job No. 1878-C (Box 56)
    - Wright Aeronautical Corporation, New South Manufacturing Building, East Paterson, NJ, (1941-1943), Job No. 1880-D (Box 56)
    - Wright Aeronautical Corporation, New East Manufacturing Building Addition, East Paterson, NJ, (1941-1942), Job No. 1880-E (Box 56)
    - Wright Aeronautical Corporation, New Overpass Bridge and Clock House, East Paterson, NJ, (1942), Job No. 1880-F (Box 56)
    - Wright Aeronautical Corporation, Substation and Switch House, East Paterson, NJ, (1942), Job No. 1880-H (Box 56)
    - Wright Aeronautical Corporation, South Manufacturing Building Addition, East Paterson, NJ, (1942-1943), Job No. 1880-J (Box 56)
    - Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Steel Blade Propeller Plant, Beaver, PA, (1941-1942), Job No. 1882 (Box 56)
    - General Motors Corporation, Buick Motor Division, Aviation Engine Plant, Melrose Park, IL, (1941), Job No. 1883, 3 folders (Box 56)
    - Hudson Motor Car Company, U.S. Naval Ordinance Plant, Centerline, MI, (1941-1942), Job No. 1884, 3 folders (Box 56)
    - Hudson Motor Car Company, U.S. Naval Ordinance Plant, Centerline, MI, (1941-1942), Job No. 1884, 10 folders (Box 57)
    - Thompson Aircraft Products, Inc., Manufacturing Building, Euclid, OH, (1941-1942), Job No. 1885, 3 folders (Box 57)
    - Thompson Aircraft Products, Inc., Manufacturing Plant No. 2, Euclid, OH, (1942), Job No. 1885-E (Box 57)
    - Thompson Aircraft Products, Inc., Personnel and Service Building, Euclid, OH, (1942), Job No. 1885-L (Box 57)
    - Thompson Aircraft Products, Inc., Forge Shop Addition, Euclid, OH, (1951), Job No. 1885-P (Box 57)
    - Thompson Aircraft Products, Inc., Manufacturing Building Addition, Euclid, OH, (1951-1952), Job No. 1885-Q, 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Thompson Aircraft Products, Inc., Manufacturing Building Addition for Fork Lift Truck Storage, Euclid, OH, (1952), Job No. 1885-S (Box 57)
    - Thompson Aircraft Products, Inc., Boiler House Additions and Alterations, Euclid, OH, (1952-1953), Job No. 1885-T (Box 57)
    - The Glenn L. Martin Company, Manufacturing Building, Omaha, NE, (1941), Job No. 1886 (Box 57)
    - Ford Motor Company Willow Run Bomber Plant, Ypsilanti, Michigan (1941-1943) Job No. 1888
      - Construction of Plant, 814 prints (black-and-white; 8x10-inch) (Box 5)
        (prints by unknown photographer)
        - 1, #1-42, Spring and Early Summer 1941; 40 prints (Box 5)
        - 2, #43-82, Spring and Summer1941, 40 prints (Box 5)
        - 3, #83-122, Summer 1941; 40 prints (Box 5)
        - 4, #123-164, Summer 1941; 42 prints (Box 5)
        - 5, #165-194, Late Summer 1941-10/21/1941; 39 prints (ten without numbers by Stegeman) (Box 5)
        - 6, #195-234, 11/3/1941-12/1/1941; 40 prints (Box 5)
        - 7, #235-275, 12/1/1941-1/5/1942; 41 prints (Box 5)
        - 8, #276-315, 1/5/1942-2/2/1942; 40 prints (Box 5)
        - 9, #316-355, 2/2/1942-2/18/1942; 40 prints (Box 5)
        - 10, #356-396, 2/18/1942-4/2/1942; 41 prints (Box 6)
        - 11, #397-435, 4/2/1942-4/23/1942; 40 prints (Box 6)
        - 12, #436-476, 4/23/1942-5/12/1942; 44 prints (Box 6)
        - 13, #473-523, 5/19/1942-6/5/1942; 50 prints (Box 6)
        - 14, #524-571, 6/19/1942-7/6/1942; 46 prints (Box 6)
        - 15, #572-593, 7/1942-8/19/1942; 19 prints (Box 6)
        - 16, #595-639, 9/1942-1943; 39 prints (Box 6)
        - 17, #640-694, 1943; 41 prints (Box 6)
        - 18, #695-734, 1943; 40 prints (Box 6)
        - 19, #735-775, 1943-11/4/1943; 40 prints (Box 6)
        - 20, #776-827, 11/12/1943-12/24/1943; 52 prints (Box 6)
      - Construction of Plant by unknown photographer, 3-1/2x4-3/4-inch, black-and-white prints with typed descriptions on reverse side
        - 1, 9/12/1941-10/21/1941; 40 prints (Box 6)